vietson.com 2011-09-25

# Privacy Policy at VIETSON

## PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes the personal information collected about users of the online game service accessible via the Website located at vietson.com and related URLs (the "Service") and how such information may be used or disclosed by vietson.com. ("Vietson").

The term "You" (and its variants) refers to You as a user of the Service and the term "Us" (and its variants) refers to Vietson. 

#### Overview

As part of the operation of the Service We collect and may disclose information about You. By accepting the vietson.com Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, You consent to Our use and disclosure of Your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the vietson.com Terms of Use.

#### A Special Note About Children

Please note that individuals under the age of 18 may not submit any personal information to Us or otherwise use the Service. 

#### Information We Collect

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Service. "Cookies" are small files placed on Your hard drive that assist Us in providing customized services. Certain features of the Service are only available with the use of a "cookie." We use this information to determine Our members' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve You and other members. This information may include the URL of the website that You visited prior to the Service (whether this URL is on the Service or not), the URL of the website You next go to (whether this URL is on the Service or not), what browser You are using and Your Internet Protocol address. Most cookies are "session cookies" meaning that they are automatically deleted from Your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free not to accept cookies if Your browser permits. 

We may use a third party advertising company to serve ads on Our behalf across the Internet. That advertising company may also collect anonymous information about Your visits to the Service. This is primarily accomplished through the use of a technology device, commonly referred to as a Web beacon, cookie or an action tag, which is placed on various Web pages within the Service or in an HTML e-mail that allows the third party advertising company to collect anonymous information. There may also be a number of services offered by external service providers that help You use the Service. If You choose to use these optional services and in doing so disclose information to the external service providers or grant them permission to collect information about You, then their use of Your information will be governed by their private policies, if any.

#### How We Use Personal Information

We use information in the data files We maintain about You, and the other information We obtain from Your current and past activities on the Service to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce Our Terms of Use. We may review the data of multiple members to identify problems or resolve disputes.

We may use personally identifiable information, data files and other information about You including but not limited to images, video recordings, and audio recordings to improve Our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze usage of the Service, improve Our content and product offerings, and customize the Service content, layout, and features. 

We may use Your information to contact You and to deliver information to You that may be targeted to Your interests, such as banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to Your use of the Service. You agree to receive this information. If You do not wish to receive this information, You may opt out of the receipt of certain communications. To learn how to do so please go to the "Help" section of the Service. 

#### Email Policies

By default, we will send you weekly updates of various site information, a variety of transactional emails such as when users send you a message and the occasional site announcement. 

#### Inviting Friends

Inviting friends to vietson.com is always completely optional. When you choose to invite friends, we will send an email to the addresses you enter indicating that it is a message from you. We will share your name and email address with anyone you invite so that they know who the invitation is coming from. If a friend does not respond to the initial invitation after a little while, we will send up to one reminder messages on your behalf. 

For your convenience, vietson.com offers the ability to import email addresses from common address books such as Hotmail/Yahoo/Gmail/AOL. If you choose to use this feature, we will access your address book using the login details that you provide. We access your address book only once to retrieve your friends' information so that you may select whom to invite. We do not store your login details nor do we use them for any other purpose then to retrieve your contacts. We never send invitations to contacts you do not explicitly select and your invitations are the only email we will ever send to your friends unless they register to join the site. 

If you have accidentally sent invitations you did not intend - please contact us and we can cancel the reminder message. 

#### Our Disclosure of Your Information

Although we use industry-standard efforts to protect the personal information We collect via the Service, we cannot guarantee that this information will not be accessed by the government or third parties in certain circumstances. We may be required by law to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties.  In addition, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications and members may abuse or misuse Your information that they collect from the Service. Accordingly, You should not expect that Your personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private in all circumstances. 

We do not sell personally identifiable information about You to third parties (provided that we may sell such information to a third party in connection with an acquisition of all or part of our business). However, the following describes some of the ways that Your personally identifiable information may be used or disclosed.

We aggregate personally identifiable information of Our members and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing and promotional purposes. We do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify You personally. We do not disclose certain information, such as Your name, email address, password, credit card number and bank account number, to marketing advertisers. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on Our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. 

We may require that you submit certain financial information, including Your credit card billing information. We will use this information to bill You for use of Our Services and products. By making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity or transaction that uses financial information on the Service, You consent to Our providing Your financial information to Our service providers and to such third parties as We determine necessary to support and process Your transactions. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process and support Your transactions. By purchasing, or registering for, or making reservations for products or services of third parties offered on the Service, or by participating in programs offered on the Service that are administered by third parties and that require You to submit financial information in order to use them, You consent to Our providing Your financial information to those third parties. These third parties will be authorized to use Your financial information in accordance with Our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which We have no control, and You agree that We are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. 

We may share data collected via the Service, including personally identifiable information about You, with Our parent, affiliates, or subsidiaries. Our parent, affiliates and subsidiaries will follow privacy practices no less protective of such personal information than Our practices described in this Privacy Policy. It is possible that We could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such merger or acquisition occur, We would share some or all of Your personal information with the merger partner or acquiring party. The acquiring entity or newly combined entity will follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy with respect to such information. 

We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries and with third parties to enforce laws. You authorize Us to disclose any information about You to law enforcement and other government officials as We in Our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with any investigation of fraud or other activity that is illegal or may expose Us or You to liability. 

#### Your Use of Other Members' Information

Our services may include access to instant messaging and chat rooms. As a member You have access to members' identification numbers or user names and You might gain access to other contact information of other members through the use of the Service.  You may not use such information in any manner that is not authorized by Us and the applicable member. In all cases, You must give members an opportunity to remove their information from Your information databases, including email lists.  Under no circumstances may You disclose personally identifiable information about another member to any third party without Our consent and the consent of such other member. You may not add a member to an mail list (email or physical mail) without that memberâ€™s express consent. 

#### Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Profile

After registration You can review and change the information You submitted during registration. For instructions on how to do so visit the "Help" section of the Service. 

Upon Your request We will remove Your membership data from Our active databases as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with Our policy and applicable law. To learn how to hide or remove Your profile so that others cannot view it visit the "Help" section of the Service. We may retain in Our files information You have requested be removed from Our active databases for certain purposes, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce the Terms of Use. Moreover, such prior information may never be completely removed from Our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored â€˜back up' systems. You should not expect that all of Your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from Our databases in response to Your request.

#### Control of Your Password

You are responsible for all actions taken with Your login information and password, including any fees or charges incurred based on such use. If You choose to share this information with a third party, You are responsible for all actions taken with Your login information and password by such third party. If You believe your password has been disclosed to third parties or otherwise compromised in any way You should immediately change Your password.

#### Third Party Use of Information

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information We collect from You. If You disclose Your personal information to other parties, whether via the Service or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information You disclose to them. We do not control the privacy policies of any third parties so You should investigate their policies before You disclose Your personal information to them.

#### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time based on changes in the law, Your comments, or Our need to accurately reflect Our data collection and disclosure practices. We will notify you of such revisions and such revisions shall become effective in accordance with the procedures for revising the Terms of Use.
